koyuki-hakuba.com 2012-05-04

# Privacy Policy - B&B Koyuki: Bed and Breakfast Accommodation in Hakuba Japan

B&B Koyuki, which is accessible at [www.koyuki-hakuba.com](http://www.koyuki-hakuba.com/) and [www.koyukihakuba.com](http://www.koyukihakuba.com/), is an accommodation service provider in Hakuba, Japan and we care deeply about online privacy. If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please [contact us via e-mail](http://www.koyuki-hakuba.com/component/option,com_qcontacts/Itemid,114/catid,42/view,category/).

## Information Collection and Use

Koyuki-Hakuba.com collects user submitted information such as name, email address, and home address for reservation requests and to send booking confirmations to those requesting a room at B&B Koyuki.

Koyuki-Hakuba.com also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address and browser type, from users and visitors to the site. This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes.

## Use of Cookies

Koyuki-Hakuba.com uses cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information. We use this information to improve our web page content based on browser type and user profile information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set -  each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.

## Links

Koyuki-Hakuba.com contains links to sites. Koyuki-Hakuba.com is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on Koyuki-Hakuba.com.

## Koyuki Blog

Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post comments to our Blog that that information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications.

## Correcting/Updating or Removing Information

Koyuki-Hakuba.com users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account and accessing features such as Edit Profile and Account Info.
